schoolrack.com 2008-11-01

# SchoolRack » Privacy Policy

Your information is safe with us Our privacy policy is simple: we will never share any of your information with anyone for any reason. 

#### What personal information does SchoolRack collect?

SchoolRack Inc. fully respects your privacy. During registration, the only personal information SchoolRack requires is: your display name and e-mail address. You may volunteer additional information once you are logged in to your personal account. Any personal information you provide to us will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of SchoolRack under any circumstance.

#### Credit card details

SchoolRack Inc. will ask for credit card details for premium SchoolRack accounts. All credit card transactions will be securely handled through PayPal®. 

#### External Sites

SchoolRack Inc. is not responsible for the content on external websites (any URL not beginning with http://www.schoolrack.com). You are advised to read the privacy policy of external websites before disclosing any personal information to them.

#### Cookies 

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows SchoolRack to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and SchoolRack does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to SchoolRack and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through SchoolRack have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For inquiries or concerns, reach SchoolRack from the Contact page.

_Last Updated May, 2007_
